Hello.
In this next lecture, we need to fix a couple of problems with our apple projector.
If I go play and I shoot my apple projector at the mushroom enemy, my mushroom enemy will be damaged
when the apple projector hits its box curtain.
That's obviously incorrect.
So we need to fix it.
So in order to do that, if we open up our mushroom enemy and select the box, if we go over to Collision
Presets, we can see that the object type is set to a world dynamic and its collision presets are overlap
or dynamic.
If I go over to my apple projector and select its fair, its collision free text or other app or dynamic
and its object type is also well dynamic.
This means my apple projector is overlapping this box and when it does, it damages my player character.
So in my apple projector under Collision Presets, change it to be custom and then set it to a ignores
wild dynamic.
I mushroom beeps box is wild dynamic.
So by doing this our apple will now ignore the box in our mushroom character like a compile play.
And now if I shoot my apple projectile it ignores the box and it will only hit the enemy mushroom character.
Nice.
Okay.
So I think my mushroom projectile attack damaged my player character multiple times.
In order to fix that, let's go back to our mushroom protractor.
And after we apply damage, just drag off here and look for do once.
That way this can only damage us once, so we're going to compile and save that.
There's one more thing I want to fix about my range enemy.
If I go play and I go up and attack my range enemy.
Is still going to try and attack me even when it's getting damaged.
So to prevent that, if I go back to my mushroom blueprint whenever I damage my enemy, I launch them
up in the air.
So I'm going to make it so that if my mushroom is in the air, it can't try and attack me.
So if we just drag off this is that and look for the OR Boolean, and then if I drag in my character
movement and drag and the ball is falling.
So if my character is in the air, they're not going to be able to try and attack me.
So I just hook this up here and go compile and go play.
That way I should be able to constantly attack my range enemy because before it's kind of hard to damage
the enemy if it's always attacking you.